var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "forever",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ābāanā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their forefathers",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ābāuhum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُوكَ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yatūka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "will bring",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "(will be) brought",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "they will give",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْتُمُوهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you have given them",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "ātaytumūhunna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْتُمُ",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "waātaytumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "and He gave you",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "waātākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِ",
        "answer": "He (had) given",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "yu'ti",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are given",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "ūtītum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْتَوْهُ",
        "answer": "you are given it",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "tu'tawhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We gave him",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He (has) given you",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "ātākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "He grants",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "yu'tīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "wayu'tūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "are given",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "آثَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their footsteps",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "āthārihim",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "[the] sin",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِإِثْمٍ",
        "answer": "to sin",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "li-ith'min",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِثْمِي",
        "answer": "with my sin",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "bi-ith'mī",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِثْمِكَ",
        "answer": "and your sin",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-ith'mika",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمِ",
        "answer": "[the] sin",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ith'mi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِثْمَ",
        "answer": "the sinful",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِثْمًا",
        "answer": "(of) sin",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ith'man",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآثِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the sinners",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-āthimīna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُجُورَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "their bridal due",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ujūrahunna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "and a reward",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْلِ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ajli",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "(to) anyone",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدِهِمَا",
        "answer": "one of them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aḥadihimā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدَكُمُ",
        "answer": "one of you",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aḥadakumu",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَ",
        "answer": "took",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُذُوهُ",
        "answer": "[so] take it",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fakhudhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We took",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤَاخِذُكُمُ",
        "answer": "will call you to account",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "yuākhidhukumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤَاخِذُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will call you to account",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "yuākhidhukum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوهَا",
        "answer": "they take it",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhūhā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "they (would have) taken them",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhūhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخِذُونِي",
        "answer": "Take me",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "ittakhidhūnī",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَّخِذِي",
        "answer": "ones (who are) taking",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "muttakhidhī",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخِرِنَا",
        "answer": "and last of us",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "waākhirinā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِ",
        "answer": "the Last",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiri",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخَرِ",
        "answer": "the other",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "l-ākhari",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرَانِ",
        "answer": "two others",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "ākharāni",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآخَرَانِ",
        "answer": "then (let) two others",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "faākharāni",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخِي",
        "answer": "and my brother",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-akhī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his brother",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِي",
        "answer": "(of) my brother",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "akhī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "then when",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأُذُنَ",
        "answer": "and the ear",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wal-udhuna",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأُذُنِ",
        "answer": "for the ear",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "bil-udhuni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِهِ",
        "answer": "by His permission",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nihi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِي",
        "answer": "by My permission",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nī",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِي",
        "answer": "by My permission",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nī",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِي",
        "answer": "by My permission",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nī",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِي",
        "answer": "by My permission",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'nī",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْسَ",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tasa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْسَ",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tasa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْفَكُونَ",
        "answer": "they are deluded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yu'fakūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكَلَ",
        "answer": "ate (it)",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "akala",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "So eat",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَكَلُوا",
        "answer": "surely they (would have) eaten",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "la-akalū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلَانِ",
        "answer": "eat",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yakulāni",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "And eat",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَأْكُلَ",
        "answer": "we eat",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "nakula",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكَّالُونَ",
        "answer": "devourers",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "akkālūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْلِهِمُ",
        "answer": "and eating",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "wa-aklihimu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْلِهِمُ",
        "answer": "and their eating",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "wa-aklihimu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "610",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "611",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "612",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "613",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "614",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "615",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "you (who)",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "you (who)",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(for) those who",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the ones",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those ",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(the) God",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(as) two gods",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ilāhayni",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "869",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "870",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "871",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "872",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "873",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "874",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "875",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "876",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "877",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "878",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "879",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "880",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "881",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "882",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "883",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "884",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "885",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "886",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "887",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "888",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "889",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "890",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "891",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "892",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "893",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "894",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "895",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "896",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "897",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "898",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "899",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "900",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "901",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "902",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "903",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "904",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "905",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "906",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "907",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(does) Allah",
        "pcklId": "908",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "909",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "910",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(against) Allah",
        "pcklId": "911",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "912",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "913",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "914",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "915",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "916",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "917",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "918",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "919",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "920",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "921",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "922",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "923",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "924",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "925",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "926",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "927",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "928",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "929",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "930",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "931",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "932",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "933",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "934",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "935",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "936",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "937",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "938",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "943",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "944",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "945",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah ",
        "pcklId": "946",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "947",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "948",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "949",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "950",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "951",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "952",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "953",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "954",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "955",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "956",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "957",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "958",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "959",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "960",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "961",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "with Allah",
        "pcklId": "962",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "963",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "964",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "965",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "966",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "967",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "while Allah",
        "pcklId": "968",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "969",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "970",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "971",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "972",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "973",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "974",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "975",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "976",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "977",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "978",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "979",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "980",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "981",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "982",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "983",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "984",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "985",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "986",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "987",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "988",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "989",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "990",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "991",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "992",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "993",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "994",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "995",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "996",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "997",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "998",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "999",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1000",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1001",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1002",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1003",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1004",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1005",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1006",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1007",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1008",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1009",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1010",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1011",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1012",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1013",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1014",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "To Allah (belongs)",
        "pcklId": "1015",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُمَّ",
        "answer": "O Allah",
        "pcklId": "2847",
        "tlit": "l-lahuma",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "towards you",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "towards me",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "towards you",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "towards Him",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "and to",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرْتَنِي",
        "answer": "You commanded me",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "amartanī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرٍ",
        "answer": "a decision",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "amrin",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his deed",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمَّهُ",
        "answer": "and his mother",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-ummahu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمُّهُ",
        "answer": "And his mother",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-ummuhu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِّيَ",
        "answer": "and my mother",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-ummiya",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a community",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِّينَ",
        "answer": "(those) coming",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "āmmīna",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you believe",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "waāmantum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "tu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we believe",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "(had) believed",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we have believed",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "we believe",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "nu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنُوا",
        "answer": "and they believe",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "waāmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنُوا",
        "answer": "and believe",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "waāmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْإِيمَانِ",
        "answer": "the faith ",
        "pcklId": "617",
        "tlit": "bil-īmāni",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "692",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "693",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the believers",
        "pcklId": "694",
        "tlit": "bil-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "695",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "696",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "697",
        "tlit": "mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "698",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنَاتِ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "851",
        "tlit": "l-mu'mināti",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْفَ",
        "answer": "and the nose",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-anfa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَنْفِ",
        "answer": "for the nose",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-anfi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "O People",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yāahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "O People",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yāahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلُ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ahlu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "O People",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yāahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "O People",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yāahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "O People",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yāahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "your families",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ahlīkum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَوَّلِنَا",
        "answer": "for first of us",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "li-awwalinā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أُولِي",
        "answer": "O men",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "yāulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَأْوَاهُ",
        "answer": "and his abode",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wamawāhu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّدْتُكَ",
        "answer": "I strengthened you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ayyadttuka",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs ",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Verses",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "biāyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Verses",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "āyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآيَةً",
        "answer": "and a sign",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "waāyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "Surely evil",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "labi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "Surely, evil",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "labi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "Surely, evil",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "labi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "Surely evil",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "labi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْحَثُ",
        "answer": "it (was) scratching",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yabḥathu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the sea",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَحِيرَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Bahirah",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "baḥīratin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدَ",
        "answer": "made clear",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tub'da",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدَ",
        "answer": "it would be made clear",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tub'da",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْدُونَ",
        "answer": "you reveal",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tub'dūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُبْرِئُ",
        "answer": "and you heal",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "watub'ri-u",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the land",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبِرِّ",
        "answer": "[the] righteousness",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-biri",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَبْرَصَ",
        "answer": "and the leper",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-abraṣa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُوا",
        "answer": "they stretch",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَسَطْتَ",
        "answer": "you stretch",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "basaṭta",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَاسِطٍ",
        "answer": "stretch",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "bibāsiṭin",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَبْسُوطَتَانِ",
        "answer": "(are) stretched out",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "mabsūṭatāni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرٌ",
        "answer": "human beings",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "basharun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشِيرٍ",
        "answer": "bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "bashīrin",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "bashīrun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَعَثْنَا",
        "answer": "and We appointed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wabaʿathnā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَعَثَ",
        "answer": "Then (was) sent",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fabaʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدُ",
        "answer": "after (that)",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "baʿdu",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضِ",
        "answer": "some",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "baʿḍi",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَعْضِ",
        "answer": "for some",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "bibaʿḍi",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Some of them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "(to) others",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَغْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "and [the] hatred",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-baghḍāa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَغْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "and [the] hatred",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-baghḍāa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَغْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "and [the] hatred",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-baghḍāa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْغُونَ",
        "answer": "they seek",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yabghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْتَغُونَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yabtaghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "and seek",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'taghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلِّغْ",
        "answer": "Convey",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "balligh",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَّغْتَ",
        "answer": "you (have) conveyed",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ballaghta",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاغُ",
        "answer": "(is to) convey (the Message)",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-balāghu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاغُ",
        "answer": "the conveyance",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-balāghu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَالِغَ",
        "answer": "reaching",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "bāligha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَبْلُوَكُمْ",
        "answer": "to test you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "liyabluwakum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَبْلُوَنَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "Surely will test you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "layabluwannakumu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءُ",
        "answer": "(the) children",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "abnāu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَيْ",
        "answer": "(of) two sons",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ib'nay",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنِ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنِ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(from the) Children",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(from the) Children",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَهِيمَةُ",
        "answer": "the quadruped",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bahīmatu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبُوءَ",
        "answer": "you be laden",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tabūa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَابَ",
        "answer": "(through) the gate",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-bāba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتَ",
        "answer": "(to) the House",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-bayta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتَ",
        "answer": "the House",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-bayta",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "making clear",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "he makes clear",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "We make clear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَيِّنُ",
        "answer": "makes clear",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yubayyinu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمُ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "baynahumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between both of them",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between them",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "between us",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَ",
        "answer": "and between",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "wabayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was) between",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was) between",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was) before",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمُ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "baynahumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمُ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "baynakumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِكُمْ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "baynikum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear Signs",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with the clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "clearly",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "seek",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِ",
        "answer": "beneath",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taḥti",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "is recited",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yut'lā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتْلُ",
        "answer": "And recite",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-ut'lu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَتْمَمْتُ",
        "answer": "and I have completed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-atmamtu",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُتِمَّ",
        "answer": "and to complete",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waliyutimma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابُوا",
        "answer": "repent",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tābū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repented",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "will turn in forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yatūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "turned",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُونَ",
        "answer": "they turn in repentance",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yatūbūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتِيهُونَ",
        "answer": "they will wander",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatīhūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَالِثُ",
        "answer": "(is the) third",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thālithu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) three",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "thalāthatin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثَةِ",
        "answer": "(for) three",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "thalāthati",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "(for) a price",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَنًا",
        "answer": "a price",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "thamanan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ith'nay",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَانِ",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ith'nāni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَثَابَهُمُ",
        "answer": "So rewarded them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-athābahumu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثُوبَةً",
        "answer": "(as) recompense",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "mathūbatan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَبَّارِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) tyrannical strength",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "jabbārīna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجُرُوحَ",
        "answer": "and (for) wounds",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-jurūḥa",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَوَارِحِ",
        "answer": "(your) hunting animals",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-jawāriḥi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْرِمَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "incite you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajrimannakum",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْرِمَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "prevent you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yajrimannakum",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flows",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flows",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) recompense",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(the) recompense",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "(as) a recompense",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) reward",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَزَاءٌ",
        "answer": "then penalty",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "fajazāon",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَجْعَلَ",
        "answer": "to make",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "liyajʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "He placed",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and made you",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He (would have) made you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "lajaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "Has (been) made",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "has (been) made",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْمَعُ",
        "answer": "will (be) gathered",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yajmaʿu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاجْتَنِبُوهُ",
        "answer": "so avoid it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-ij'tanibūhu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنُبًا",
        "answer": "(in) a state of ceremonial impurity",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "junuban",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنَاحٌ",
        "answer": "any sin",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "junāḥun",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَجَانِفٍ",
        "answer": "inclining",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mutajānifin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(to) gardens",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "(to) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "jannāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(with) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٌ",
        "answer": "(are) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "jannātun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهِدُوا",
        "answer": "and strive hard",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wajāhidū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَاهِدُونَ",
        "answer": "striving",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yujāhidūna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَهْدَ",
        "answer": "strongest",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "jahda",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِيَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of the time of) ignorance",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-jāhiliyati",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُجِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "was (the) response you received",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ujib'tum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "has come",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "(has) come to us",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "jāanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "jāathum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوكَ",
        "answer": "they come to you",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "jāūka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكَ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "jāaka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they come to you",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "jāūkum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "came (to) us",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "jāanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you came to them",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ji'tahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "whom He loves",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbuhum",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحِبُّونَهُ",
        "answer": "and they love Him",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wayuḥibbūnahu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحِبَّاؤُهُ",
        "answer": "and His beloved",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥibbāuhu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَحْبَارُ",
        "answer": "and the scholars",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-aḥbāru",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَحْبَارُ",
        "answer": "and the religious scholars",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-aḥbāru",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْبِسُونَهُمَا",
        "answer": "Detain both of them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥbisūnahumā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَ",
        "answer": "(are) wasted",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭa",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَتْ",
        "answer": "Became worthless",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْذَرُوا",
        "answer": "then beware",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-iḥ'dharū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحْذَرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and beware of them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-iḥ'dharhum",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحْذَرُوا",
        "answer": "and beware",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-iḥ'dharū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَارِبُونَ",
        "answer": "wage war",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuḥāribūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْحَرْبِ",
        "answer": "of [the] war",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lil'ḥarbi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٍ",
        "answer": "difficulty",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥarajin",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْرِيرُ",
        "answer": "freeing",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "taḥrīru",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَرِّفُونَ",
        "answer": "They distort",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yuḥarrifūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَرِّفُونَ",
        "answer": "They distort",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuḥarrifūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرِّمَتْ",
        "answer": "Are made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥurrimat",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "(has) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحَرِّمُوا",
        "answer": "make unlawful",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuḥarrimū",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُرِّمَ",
        "answer": "and is made unlawful",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waḥurrima",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "the sacred",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "the Sacred",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "the Sacred",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "[the] sacred",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرُمٌ",
        "answer": "(are in) Ihram",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ḥurumun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرُمٌ",
        "answer": "(are in) Ihram",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ḥurumun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُرُمًا",
        "answer": "(are in) Ihram",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ḥuruman",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحَرَّمَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "muḥarramatun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِزْبَ",
        "answer": "(the) party",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥiz'ba",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزُنْكَ",
        "answer": "grieve you",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaḥzunka",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَسِبُوا",
        "answer": "And they thought",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waḥasibū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسْبُنَا",
        "answer": "Sufficient for us",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ḥasbunā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِسَابِ",
        "answer": "(in taking) account",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-ḥisābi",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسَنُوا",
        "answer": "and do good",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsanū",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "goodly",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْصِنِينَ",
        "answer": "being chaste",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "muḥ'ṣinīna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُحْصَنَاتُ",
        "answer": "And the chaste women",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wal-muḥ'ṣanātu",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُحْصَنَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the chaste women",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-muḥ'ṣanātu",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَضَرَ",
        "answer": "approaches",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥaḍara",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَظًّا",
        "answer": "a part",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥaẓẓan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَظًّا",
        "answer": "a part",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥaẓẓan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحْفَظُوا",
        "answer": "And guard",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-iḥ'faẓū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُحْفِظُوا",
        "answer": "they were entrusted",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "us'tuḥ'fiẓū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَحَقَّا",
        "answer": "(were) guilty",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "is'taḥaqqā",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَحَقَّ",
        "answer": "have a lawful right",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "is'taḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) truer",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in [the] truth",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَقٍّ",
        "answer": "(had) right",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "biḥaqqin",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "decrees",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "then judge",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-uḥ'kum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكَمْتَ",
        "answer": "you judge",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥakamta",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "then judge",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-uḥ'kum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "judged",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "judge",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yaḥkum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "judge",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yaḥkum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلْيَحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "And let judge",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "walyaḥkum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "judge",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yaḥkum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحْكُمْ",
        "answer": "So judge",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fa-uḥ'kum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "احْكُمْ",
        "answer": "you judge",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "uḥ'kum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "judging",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَكِّمُونَكَ",
        "answer": "they appoint you a judge",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yuḥakkimūnaka",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُكْمُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Command",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ḥuk'mu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَحُكْمَ",
        "answer": "Is it then the judgment",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "afaḥuk'ma",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُكْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) judgment",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ḥuk'man",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِكْمَةَ",
        "answer": "and the wisdom",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥik'mata",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "ḥakīmun",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have sworn",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥalaftum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you come out of Ihram",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥalaltum",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّتْ",
        "answer": "Are made lawful",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "uḥillat",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحِلُّوا",
        "answer": "violate",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tuḥillū",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّ",
        "answer": "(is) made lawful",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "uḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّ",
        "answer": "Are made lawful",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "uḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّ",
        "answer": "are made lawful",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "uḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَلَّ",
        "answer": "has (been) made lawful",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aḥalla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُحِلَّ",
        "answer": "Is made lawful",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "uḥilla",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِلٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) lawful",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ḥillun",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِلٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) lawful",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ḥillun",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلَالًا",
        "answer": "lawful",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ḥalālan",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحِلِّي",
        "answer": "being permitted",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "muḥillī",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Forbearing",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmun",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَامٍ",
        "answer": "a Hami",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥāmin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَوَارِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "the disciples",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ḥawāriyīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَوَارِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "the disciples",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ḥawāriyūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "(at the) time (of making)",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَاهَا",
        "answer": "saves it",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aḥyāhā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَا",
        "answer": "he has saved",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "aḥyā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيثُ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-khabīthu",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيثِ",
        "answer": "(of) the evil",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-khabīthi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْدَانٍ",
        "answer": "secret lovers",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "akhdānin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُوا",
        "answer": "they leave",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yakhrujū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُوا",
        "answer": "they leave",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yakhrujū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُوا",
        "answer": "they come out",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yakhrujū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرَجُوا",
        "answer": "went out",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "kharajū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُخْرِجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and brings them out",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wayukh'rijuhum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "you bring forth",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "tukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَارِجِينَ",
        "answer": "will come out",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "bikhārijīna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِزْيٌ",
        "answer": "disgrace",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "khiz'yun",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِزْيٌ",
        "answer": "(is) disgrace",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "khiz'yun",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) losers",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) losers",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَوْهُمْ",
        "answer": "fear them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "takhshawhum",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْشَوْنِ",
        "answer": "but fear Me",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'shawni",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَوُا",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "takhshawū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْشَوْنِ",
        "answer": "but fear Me",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'shawni",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخْشَىٰ",
        "answer": "We fear",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nakhshā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْفُونَ",
        "answer": "conceal",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tukh'fūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "will abide",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْتَلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "differing",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "takhtalifūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَافٍ",
        "answer": "opposite sides",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "khilāfin",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "He creates",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yakhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "He created",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "you make",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "takhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "had passed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَمْرُ",
        "answer": "the intoxicants",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-khamru",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَمْرِ",
        "answer": "intoxicants",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-khamri",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَخْمَصَةٍ",
        "answer": "hunger",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "makhmaṣatin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِنْزِيرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the swine",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-khinzīri",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْخَنَازِيرَ",
        "answer": "and [the] swines",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-khanāzīra",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنْخَنِقَةُ",
        "answer": "and that which is strangled (to death)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-mun'khaniqatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "feared (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yakhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yakhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُهُ",
        "answer": "fears Him",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yakhāfuhu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُوا",
        "answer": "they would fear",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yakhāfū",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَائِنَةٍ",
        "answer": "treachery",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khāinatin",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(are) best",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرَاتِ",
        "answer": "(to) the good",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-khayrāti",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْبَارِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your backs",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "adbārikum",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَدْخُلَهَا",
        "answer": "will enter it",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "nadkhulahā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَخَلْتُمُوهُ",
        "answer": "you have entered it",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "dakhaltumūhu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَدْخُلَهَا",
        "answer": "will enter it",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nadkhulahā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَخَلُوا",
        "answer": "they entered",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "dakhalū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَأُدْخِلَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and I will surely admit you",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wala-ud'khilannakum",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَأَدْخَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and surely We (would have) admitted them",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wala-adkhalnāhum",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْخِلَنَا",
        "answer": "will admit us",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "yud'khilanā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَاخِلُونَ",
        "answer": "enter (it)",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "dākhilūna",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّمْعِ",
        "answer": "the tears",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-damʿi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالدَّمُ",
        "answer": "and the blood",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-damu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) closer",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "adnā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَائِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "a misfortune",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dāiratun",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَامُوا",
        "answer": "as long as they are",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dāmū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "long as you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dum'tum",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُمْتُ",
        "answer": "as long as I",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "dum'tu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "dīnikum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "dīnakum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينًا",
        "answer": "(as) a religion",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "dīnan",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِهِ",
        "answer": "his religion",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dīnihi",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "dīnakum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "dīnikum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُبِحَ",
        "answer": "is sacrificed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dhubiḥa",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "but mention",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "Remember",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْكُرْ",
        "answer": "Remember",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "udh'kur",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they were reminded",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they were reminded",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) remembrance",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَكَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you slaughtered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dhakkaytum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذِلَّةٍ",
        "answer": "humble",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "adhillatin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for your sins",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbikum",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُنُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their sins",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "dhunūbihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "So go",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَذُوقَ",
        "answer": "that he may taste",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "liyadhūqa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُءُوسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your heads",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "biruūsikum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَى",
        "answer": "And you see",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fatarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "And you see",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "watarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "You see",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُرِيَهُ",
        "answer": "to show him",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "liyuriyahu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "and your Lord",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "warabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "O my Lord",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "rabba",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your Lord",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "warabbakum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your Lord",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "warabbakum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرَّبَّانِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "and the Rabbis",
        "pcklId": "977",
        "tlit": "wal-rabāniyūna",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّبَّانِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "the Rabbis",
        "pcklId": "978",
        "tlit": "l-rabāniyūna",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعِينَ",
        "answer": "(for) forty",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "arbaʿīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسٌ",
        "answer": "(are an) abomination",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rij'sun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "you will return",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your return ",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلَانِ",
        "answer": "two men",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "rajulāni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْجُلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your feet",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-arjulakum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْجُلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their feet",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wa-arjuluhum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجُلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their feet",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "arjulihim",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَدَّ",
        "answer": "will be refuted",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "turadda",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْتَدُّوا",
        "answer": "turn",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tartaddū",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْتَدَّ",
        "answer": "turns back",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yartadda",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُتَرَدِّيَةُ",
        "answer": "and that which has a fatal fall",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-mutaradiyatu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "has provided you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "razaqakumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْزُقْنَا",
        "answer": "And provide us",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-ur'zuq'nā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّازِقِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the providers",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-rāziqīna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We sent",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His Message",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "risālatahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُسُلِي",
        "answer": "in My Messengers",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "birusulī",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messenger",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "rasūlunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messenger",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "rasūlunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلِ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "l-rusuli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messengers",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "rusulunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولُهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "warasūluhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلًا",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "rusulan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "any Messenger",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلُ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "l-rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولَ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "l-rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messenger",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "rasūlinā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "l-rusula",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِرَسُولِي",
        "answer": "and in My Messenger",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "wabirasūlī",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَضِيتُ",
        "answer": "and I have approved",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waraḍītu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضِيَ",
        "answer": "is pleased",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "raḍiya",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَضُوا",
        "answer": "and they are pleased",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waraḍū",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانًا",
        "answer": "and good pleasure",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِضْوَانَهُ",
        "answer": "His pleasure",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "riḍ'wānahu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرَافِقِ",
        "answer": "the elbows",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-marāfiqi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَقَبَةٍ",
        "answer": "a slave",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "raqabatin",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّقِيبَ",
        "answer": "the Watcher",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-raqība",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاكِعُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who bow down",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "rākiʿūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِمَاحُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your spears",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "warimāḥukum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُهْبَانًا",
        "answer": "and monks",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waruh'bānan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُوحِ",
        "answer": "with (the) Spirit",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "birūḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "intend",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "wish",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "urīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "They will wish",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِدِ",
        "answer": "intends",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yuridi",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِدِ",
        "answer": "will intend",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yuridi",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "intends",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "intends",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "We wish",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "nurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْتَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you doubt",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ir'tabtum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "zakah",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَزْلَامِ",
        "answer": "by divining arrows ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-azlāmi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَزْلَامُ",
        "answer": "and divining arrows",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-azlāmu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَزِيدَنَّ",
        "answer": "And surely increase",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "walayazīdanna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَزِيدَنَّ",
        "answer": "And surely increase",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "walayazīdanna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزَالُ",
        "answer": "will you cease",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tazālu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْأَلُوا",
        "answer": "ask",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tasalū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْأَلُوا",
        "answer": "you ask",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "tasalū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلَهَا",
        "answer": "asked them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "sa-alahā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَكَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to You",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبُعُ",
        "answer": "the wild animal",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-sabuʿu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَبِقُوا",
        "answer": "so race",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tabiqū",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبُلَ",
        "answer": "(to the) ways",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "subula",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His way",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "[the] way",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلسُّحْتِ",
        "answer": "of the forbidden",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lilssuḥ'ti",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّحْتَ",
        "answer": "the forbidden",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-suḥ'ta",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّحْتَ",
        "answer": "(of) the forbidden",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-suḥ'ta",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرٌ",
        "answer": "magic",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "siḥ'run",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخِطَ",
        "answer": "became angry",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sakhiṭa",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَرُّوا",
        "answer": "they had concealed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "asarrū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَارِعُونَ",
        "answer": "hasten",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yusāriʿūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَارِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they hasten",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yusāriʿūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَارِعُونَ",
        "answer": "hastening",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yusāriʿūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرِيعُ",
        "answer": "is swift",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "sarīʿu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُسْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely those who commit excesses",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "lamus'rifūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّارِقُ",
        "answer": "And (for) the male thief",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-sāriqu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّارِقَةُ",
        "answer": "and the female thief ",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wal-sāriqatu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْعَوْنَ",
        "answer": "and strive",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wayasʿawna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْعَوْنَ",
        "answer": "And they strive",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wayasʿawna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَافِحِينَ",
        "answer": "being lewd",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "musāfiḥīna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَرٍ",
        "answer": "a journey",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "safarin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاكِينَ",
        "answer": "needy people",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "masākīna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاكِينَ",
        "answer": "needy people",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "masākīna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَفَ",
        "answer": "(has) passed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "salafa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "had submitted (to Allah)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aslamū",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّلَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) the peace",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-salāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِسْلَامَ",
        "answer": "[the] Islam",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-is'lāma",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) Muslims",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "We heard",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعُوا",
        "answer": "they listen",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "samiʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْمَعُوا",
        "answer": "and listen",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wa-is'maʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَّاعُونَ",
        "answer": "They (are) listeners",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "sammāʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَّاعُونَ",
        "answer": "(and) listeners",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "sammāʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَّاعُونَ",
        "answer": "Listeners",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "sammāʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمَ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "is'ma",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسِّنَّ",
        "answer": "and the tooth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-sina",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسِّنِّ",
        "answer": "for the tooth",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-sini",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَةً",
        "answer": "years",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "sanatan",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسُؤْكُمْ",
        "answer": "it may distress you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tasu'kum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْءَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) dead body",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "sawata",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْءَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) dead body",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "sawata",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "sayyiātikum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their evil (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "sayyiātihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "(are) equal",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءَ",
        "answer": "(from) the way",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "sawāa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) even",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "sawāi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) right",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "sawāi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَائِبَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Saibah",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sāibatin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلسَّيَّارَةِ",
        "answer": "and for the travelers",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "walilssayyārati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدَّ",
        "answer": "strongest",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ashadda",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدُ",
        "answer": "(is) severe",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "shadīdu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشَرٍّ",
        "answer": "(of) worse",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bisharrin",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(are) worse",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sharrun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِرْعَةً",
        "answer": "a law",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "shir'ʿatan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكْ",
        "answer": "associates partners",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yush'rik",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكُوا",
        "answer": "(are) polytheists",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ashrakū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْتَرُوا",
        "answer": "sell",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tashtarū",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشْتَرِي",
        "answer": "we will exchange",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nashtarī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَعَائِرَ",
        "answer": "(the) rites",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "shaʿāira",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَنَآنُ",
        "answer": "(the) hatred",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shanaānu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَنَآنُ",
        "answer": "hatred",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shanaānu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْهَدْ",
        "answer": "and bear witness",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-ish'had",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهَادَةُ",
        "answer": "(Take) testimony",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "shahādatu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهَادَةَ",
        "answer": "testimony",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "shahādata",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَشَهَادَتُنَا",
        "answer": "Surely our testimony",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "lashahādatunā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهَادَتِهِمَا",
        "answer": "testimony of the other two",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "shahādatihimā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "the testimony",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "bil-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) witnesses",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "shuhadāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُهَدَاءَ",
        "answer": "witnesses",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "shuhadāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "a witness",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدٌ",
        "answer": "a Witness",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "shahīdun",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "l-shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "l-shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّهْرَ",
        "answer": "the month",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-shahra",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهْرَ",
        "answer": "and the month(s)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wal-shahra",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(had) willed",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "through something",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "bishayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْيَاءَ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "ashyāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّابِئُونَ",
        "answer": "and the Sabians",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣābiūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "and became",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "Then he became",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُصْبِحُوا",
        "answer": "Then they will become",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fayuṣ'biḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "and they became",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "they became",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدُّوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they stopped you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣaddūkum",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَصُدَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and hinders you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wayaṣuddakum",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّدُورِ",
        "answer": "(is in) the breasts",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقْتَنَا",
        "answer": "you have spoken the truth to us",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqtanā",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصَدَّقَ",
        "answer": "gives charity",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "taṣaddaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِدْقُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their truthfulness",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ṣid'quhum",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِدِّيقَةٌ",
        "answer": "(was) truthful",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ṣiddīqatun",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the truthful",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "and confirming",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "wamuṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَعِيدًا",
        "answer": "(with) earth",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣaʿīdan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْفَحْ",
        "answer": "and overlook",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'faḥ",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصَلَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they be crucified",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yuṣallabū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "and reforms",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "good deeds",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "the righteous deeds ",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "the good deeds",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] good deeds",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَمُّوا",
        "answer": "and they became deaf",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waṣammū",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَمُّوا",
        "answer": "and they became deaf",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waṣammū",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْنَعُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṣnaʿūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْنَعُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaṣnaʿūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِيبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "afflict them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yuṣībahum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِيبَنَا",
        "answer": "(may) strike us",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tuṣībanā",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصَابَتْكُمْ",
        "answer": "then befalls you",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣābatkum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةُ",
        "answer": "calamity",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "muṣībatu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصِيَامُ",
        "answer": "(that), then fasting",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "faṣiyāmu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِيَامًا",
        "answer": "(in) fasting",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣiyāman",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاصْطَادُوا",
        "answer": "then (you may) hunt",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-iṣ'ṭādū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّيْدِ",
        "answer": "(to) hunt",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ṣaydi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّيْدِ",
        "answer": "the game ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ṣaydi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّيْدَ",
        "answer": "the game",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ṣayda",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَيْدُ",
        "answer": "game",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣaydu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَيْدُ",
        "answer": "game",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ṣaydu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is) the final return",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) travel(ing)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḍarabtum",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّوكَ",
        "answer": "will they harm you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaḍurrūka",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "will harm you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaḍurrukum",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْطُرَّ",
        "answer": "(is) forced",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "uḍ'ṭurra",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "he strayed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "who went astray",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "and they have strayed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "(have gone) astray",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "and they misled",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "and farthest astray",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعِمُوا",
        "answer": "they ate",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿimū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطْعِمُونَ",
        "answer": "you feed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tuṭ'ʿimūna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَعَامُ",
        "answer": "and (the) food",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "waṭaʿāmu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَعَامُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your food",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "waṭaʿāmukum",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّعَامَ",
        "answer": "[the] food",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-ṭaʿāma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامُ",
        "answer": "feeding",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَعَامُهُ",
        "answer": "and its food",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "waṭaʿāmuhu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِطْعَامُ",
        "answer": "(is) feeding",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "iṭ'ʿāmu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّاغُوتَ",
        "answer": "the false deities",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ṭāghūta",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) rebellion",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) rebellion",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطْفَأَهَا",
        "answer": "it (was) extinguished",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aṭfa-ahā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَّلِعُ",
        "answer": "to discover",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taṭṭaliʿu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَطْمَعُ",
        "answer": "And we hope",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wanaṭmaʿu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَطْمَئِنَّ",
        "answer": "and satisfy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wataṭma-inna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُطَهِّرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "to purify you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "liyuṭahhirakum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطَهِّرَ",
        "answer": "He purifies",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yuṭahhira",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاطَّهَّرُوا",
        "answer": "then purify yourselves",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-iṭṭahharū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَوَّعَتْ",
        "answer": "Then prompted",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faṭawwaʿat",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "and we obeyed",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطِيعُوا",
        "answer": "And obey",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭīʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَطِيعُوا",
        "answer": "and obey",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-aṭīʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُ",
        "answer": "able",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالطَّيِّبُ",
        "answer": "and the good",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-ṭayibu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبًا",
        "answer": "clean",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ṭayyiban",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṭayyiban",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيِّبَاتُ",
        "answer": "the good things",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayibātu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيِّبَاتُ",
        "answer": "the good things",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayibātu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good things",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيْرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the bird",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayri",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيْرًا",
        "answer": "a bird",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṭayran",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطِّينِ",
        "answer": "the clay",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ṭīni",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "ẓul'mihi",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darknessess",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the wrong-doers",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "lilẓẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَبَدَ",
        "answer": "and (who) worshipped",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waʿabada",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you worship",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ataʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "You worship",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادُكَ",
        "answer": "(are) Your slaves",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "ʿibāduka",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُثِرَ",
        "answer": "it is discovered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿuthira",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَبَكَ",
        "answer": "impresses you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "aʿjabaka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعَجَزْتُ",
        "answer": "Am I unable",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aʿajaztu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْدِلُوا",
        "answer": "you do justice",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿdilū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْدِلُوا",
        "answer": "Be just",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "iʿ'dilū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلٍ",
        "answer": "just",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ʿadlin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلُ",
        "answer": "equivalent",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ʿadlu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدْلٍ",
        "answer": "just",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ʿadlin",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "you commit transgression",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "taʿtadū",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "transgressing",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yaʿtadūna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "transgress",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "taʿtadū",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "transgressed",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْتَدَيْنَا",
        "answer": "we have transgressed",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "iʿ'tadaynā",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَدَاوَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] enmity",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadāwata",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَدَاوَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] enmity",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadāwata",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدَاوَةً",
        "answer": "(in) enmity",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ʿadāwatan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَدَاوَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] enmity",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadāwata",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعُدْوَانِ",
        "answer": "and [the] transgression",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿud'wāni",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعُدْوَانِ",
        "answer": "and [the] transgression",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿud'wāni",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-muʿ'tadīna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(does He) punish you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibukum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "and punishes",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wayuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "He punishes",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُعَذِّبُهُ",
        "answer": "[I] will punish him",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "uʿadhibuhu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُعَذِّبُهُ",
        "answer": "I have punished",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "uʿadhibuhu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعَذِّبْهُمْ",
        "answer": "You punish them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tuʿadhib'hum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aʿriḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tuʿ'riḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَفُوا",
        "answer": "they recognized",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿarafū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَزَّرْتُمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "and you assist them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿazzartumūhum",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(are) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعِزَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(and) stern",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "aʿizzatin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَسَى",
        "answer": "But perhaps",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "faʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشَرَ",
        "answer": "(and) ten",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿashara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشَرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) ten",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ʿasharati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْصِمُكَ",
        "answer": "will protect you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿṣimuka",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَوْا",
        "answer": "they disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣaw",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "(the) great",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْفُ",
        "answer": "But forgive",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'fu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْفُو",
        "answer": "and overlooking",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wayaʿfū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَا",
        "answer": "Pardoned",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ʿafā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَا",
        "answer": "has (been) pardoned",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ʿafā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) [the] punishment",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) punishment",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَقَّدْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you contracted",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿaqqadttumu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعُقُودِ",
        "answer": "the contracts",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿuqūdi",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use reason",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "then know",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "taʿlam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "then know that",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "then know",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "that may make evident",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "liyaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "so that you may know",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "litaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "Know",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "knowing",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "and we know",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wanaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتَهُ",
        "answer": "You would have known it",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'tahu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "You know",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "taʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have taught",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "ʿallamtum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعَلِّمُونَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "you teach them",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "tuʿallimūnahunna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمَكُمُ",
        "answer": "has taught you",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "ʿallamakumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمْتُكَ",
        "answer": "I taught you",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "ʿallamtuka",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows best",
        "pcklId": "432",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "486",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّامُ",
        "answer": "(are the) Knower",
        "pcklId": "549",
        "tlit": "ʿallāmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّامُ",
        "answer": "(are) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "550",
        "tlit": "ʿallāmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمَ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "568",
        "tlit": "ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "677",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "678",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "789",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "790",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعَالَوْا",
        "answer": "Come",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "taʿālaw",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَعَمِّدًا",
        "answer": "intentionally",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mutaʿammidan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "doing",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and did",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and they do",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلُهُ",
        "answer": "his deeds",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "ʿamaluhu",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deeds",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "aʿmāluhum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلِ",
        "answer": "(the) work",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "ʿamali",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَمُوا",
        "answer": "so they became blind",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faʿamū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمُوا",
        "answer": "they became blind",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿamū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنْدَهُمُ",
        "answer": "while they (have) with them",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "waʿindahumu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Him",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "ʿindihi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادَ",
        "answer": "returned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿāda",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِيدًا",
        "answer": "a festival",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ʿīdan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعَاوَنُوا",
        "answer": "And help one another",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wataʿāwanū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعَاوَنُوا",
        "answer": "help one another",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿāwanū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَيْنَ",
        "answer": "and the eye",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿayna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَيْنِ",
        "answer": "for the eye",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿayni",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their eyes",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aʿyunahum",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرَابًا",
        "answer": "a crow",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghurāban",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُرَابِ",
        "answer": "[the] crow",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ghurābi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْرَيْنَا",
        "answer": "So We aroused",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-aghraynā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاغْسِلُوا",
        "answer": "then wash",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-igh'silū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَضِبَ",
        "answer": "and He became angry",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waghaḍiba",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرُ",
        "answer": "He forgives",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yaghfiru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَغْفِرُ",
        "answer": "and He forgives",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wayaghfiru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "You forgive",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "taghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَغْفِرُونَهُ",
        "answer": "and seek His forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wayastaghfirūnahu",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "maghfiratun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَالِبُونَ",
        "answer": "victorious",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ghālibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the victorious",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُلَّتْ",
        "answer": "Are chained",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghullat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْلُولَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) chained",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "maghlūlatun",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغْلُوا",
        "answer": "exceed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taghlū",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَائِطِ",
        "answer": "the toilet",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ghāiṭi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "in the unseen",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُيُوبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ghuyūbi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُيُوبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ghuyūbi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "to other than",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "lighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "(and) not",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِكُمْ",
        "answer": "other than you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ghayrikum",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْفَتْحِ",
        "answer": "the victory",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "bil-fatḥi",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتْرَةٍ",
        "answer": "(after) an interval (of cessation)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatratin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتِنُوكَ",
        "answer": "they tempt you away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaftinūka",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَتَهُ",
        "answer": "his trial",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fit'natahu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةٌ",
        "answer": "a trial",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fit'natun",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَفْتَدُوا",
        "answer": "to ransom themselves",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "liyaftadū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَافْرُقْ",
        "answer": "so (make a) separation",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-uf'ruq",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "farīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "and a group",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wafarīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they invent",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَادٍ",
        "answer": "(for) spreading corruption",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fasādin",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَادًا",
        "answer": "spreading corruption",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fasādan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَادًا",
        "answer": "spreading corruption",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fasādan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِسْقٌ",
        "answer": "(is) grave disobedience",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fis'qun",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "lafāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلًا",
        "answer": "Bounty",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "faḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Grace",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "faḍlu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلْ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tafʿal",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلُوهُ",
        "answer": "they did [it]",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "faʿalūhu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "doing",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "succeed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tuf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) successful",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tuf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) successful",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tuf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fawqihim",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their mouths",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bi-afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفِيضُ",
        "answer": "overflowing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tafīḍu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُقُبِّلَ",
        "answer": "and it was accepted",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fatuqubbila",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتَقَبَّلْ",
        "answer": "was accepted",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yutaqabbal",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَقَبَّلُ",
        "answer": "accepts",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yataqabbalu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقُبِّلَ",
        "answer": "will be accepted",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tuqubbila",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before him",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَقْتُلَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "Surely I will kill you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "la-aqtulannaka",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَقْتُلَنِي",
        "answer": "to kill me",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "litaqtulanī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَقْتُلَكَ",
        "answer": "to kill you",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "li-aqtulaka",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَتَلَهُ",
        "answer": "so he killed him",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "faqatalahu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلَ",
        "answer": "kills",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "qatala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلَ",
        "answer": "he has killed",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "qatala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they kill",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yaqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "kill",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "taqtulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلَهُ",
        "answer": "killed it",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "qatalahu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلَ",
        "answer": "he killed",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qatala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَتَّلُوا",
        "answer": "they be killed",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "yuqattalū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَاتِلَا",
        "answer": "and you both fight",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "faqātilā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتْلَ",
        "answer": "(to) kill",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "qatla",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِرُوا",
        "answer": "you overpower",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taqdirū",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُدُسِ",
        "answer": "the Holy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-qudusi",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَدَّسَةَ",
        "answer": "the Holy",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-muqadasata",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَتْ",
        "answer": "sent forth",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qaddamat",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرَّبَا",
        "answer": "both offered",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "qarrabā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَبُ",
        "answer": "(is) nearer",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "aqrabu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "nearest of them",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "aqrabahum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْبَانًا",
        "answer": "a sacrifice",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qur'bānan",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "a near relative",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِرَدَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] apes",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-qiradata",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْرَضْتُمُ",
        "answer": "and you loan",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-aqraḍtumu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْضًا",
        "answer": "a loan",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "qarḍan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِسِّيسِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) priests",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qissīsīna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطِ",
        "answer": "in justice",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطِ",
        "answer": "with [the] justice",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقْسِطِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who are just",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-muq'siṭīna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْسَمُوا",
        "answer": "swore",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aqsamū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُقْسِمَانِ",
        "answer": "and let them both swear",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fayuq'simāni",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُقْسِمَانِ",
        "answer": "and let them both swear",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fayuq'simāni",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَقْسِمُوا",
        "answer": "you seek division",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tastaqsimū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاسِيَةً",
        "answer": "hard",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qāsiyatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقْتَصِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "moderate",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "muq'taṣidatun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِصَاصٌ",
        "answer": "(is) retribution",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "qiṣāṣun",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْطَعُوا",
        "answer": "[then] cut off",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-iq'ṭaʿū",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَطَّعَ",
        "answer": "be cut off",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tuqaṭṭaʿa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاعِدُونَ",
        "answer": "sitting",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "qāʿidūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَفَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We sent",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waqaffaynā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنْقَلِبُوا",
        "answer": "then you will turn back",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fatanqalibū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "qulūbahum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "qulūbahum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُنَا",
        "answer": "our hearts",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "qulūbunā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَلَائِدَ",
        "answer": "the garlanded",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-qalāida",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَلَائِدَ",
        "answer": "and the garlands",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-qalāida",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a few",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you said",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "qul'tum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said (the latter)",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said (the former)",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "saying",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "saying",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "And will say",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "While said",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they are saying",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and He will say",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "then said",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "qul'ta",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقُولَ",
        "answer": "I say",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "aqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُهُ",
        "answer": "said it",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "qul'tuhu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْتُ",
        "answer": "I said",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "qul'tu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their saying",
        "pcklId": "1642",
        "tlit": "qawlihimu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you stand up",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "qum'tum",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُومَانِ",
        "answer": "stand",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaqūmāni",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقَمْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you establish",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "aqamtumu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقِيمُونَ",
        "answer": "establish",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yuqīmūna",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "had stood firmly",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "you stand firmly",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "tuqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوَّامِينَ",
        "answer": "steadfast",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "qawwāmīna",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(for) a people",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a people",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "(are) people",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for people",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "biqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a people",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَامَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(in) their place",
        "pcklId": "571",
        "tlit": "maqāmahumā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيَامًا",
        "answer": "an establishment",
        "pcklId": "589",
        "tlit": "qiyāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "lasting",
        "pcklId": "617",
        "tlit": "muqīmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) straight",
        "pcklId": "653",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "arrogant",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبَ",
        "answer": "(has been) ordained",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kataba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبْنَا",
        "answer": "We ordained",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "katabnā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَتَبْنَا",
        "answer": "And We ordained",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wakatabnā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاكْتُبْنَا",
        "answer": "so write us",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fa-uk'tub'nā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "and a Book",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "wakitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) Book",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "hiding",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yaktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "you conceal",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "taktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكْتُمُ",
        "answer": "we will conceal",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "naktumu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "most of you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aktharakum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and most of them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثْرَةُ",
        "answer": "abundance",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "kathratu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٍ",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "kathīrin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "but many",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wakathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "kathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "and deny",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wakadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they denied",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "and denied",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wakadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَذِبِ",
        "answer": "to falsehood",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "lil'kadhibi",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَذِبِ",
        "answer": "to [the] falsehood",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "lil'kadhibi",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَذِبَ",
        "answer": "the lie",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "l-kadhiba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبَا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kasabā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِسْوَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "clothing them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kis'watuhum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَعْبَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the ankles",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-kaʿbayni",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَعْبَةِ",
        "answer": "the Kabah",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-kaʿbati",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَعْبَةَ",
        "answer": "the Kabah",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-kaʿbata",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "yakfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved ",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرَ",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "kafara",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرْ",
        "answer": "disbelieves",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "yakfur",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأُكَفِّرَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely I will remove",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "la-ukaffiranna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَفَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "surely We (would have) removed",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "lakaffarnā",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "and the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "wal-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّارَةٌ",
        "answer": "an expiation",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "kaffāratun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَفَّارَتُهُ",
        "answer": "So its expiation",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "fakaffāratuhu",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّارَةُ",
        "answer": "(is the) expiation",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "kaffāratu",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّارَةٌ",
        "answer": "an expiation ",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "kaffāratun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "[the] disbelief ",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكُفْرِ",
        "answer": "with disbelief",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "bil-kuf'ri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُفْرًا",
        "answer": "and disbelief",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "wakuf'ran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُفْرًا",
        "answer": "and disbelief",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "wakuf'ran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelieving",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelieving",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَفَّ",
        "answer": "but He restrained",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fakaffa",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَفْتُ",
        "answer": "I restrained",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "kafaftu",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكَلِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "ones who train animals to hunt",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mukallibīna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلٍّ",
        "answer": "For each",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "likullin",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Every time",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Whenever",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَلِّمُ",
        "answer": "you spoke",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tukallimu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَلِمَ",
        "answer": "the words",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-kalima",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَلِمَ",
        "answer": "the words",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-kalima",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْمَلْتُ",
        "answer": "I have perfected",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "akmaltu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَكْمَهَ",
        "answer": "the born blind",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-akmaha",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَهْلًا",
        "answer": "and (in) maturity",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wakahlan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَكُونَ",
        "answer": "so you will be",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "fatakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكُونَ",
        "answer": "I can be",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "will be (for them)",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَا",
        "answer": "They both used to",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "kānā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "They had been",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they had",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(that)",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he is",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَكُونُ",
        "answer": "and it becomes",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "fatakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَكُونَ",
        "answer": "and we be",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "wanakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُ",
        "answer": "to be",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "takūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "I had",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتُ",
        "answer": "And I was",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "wakuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "You were",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) position",
        "pcklId": "1359",
        "tlit": "makānan",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَيْفَ",
        "answer": "But how can",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wakayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) understanding",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَحْمُ",
        "answer": "and flesh",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "walaḥmu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَانِ",
        "answer": "(the) tongue",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "lisāni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعِبًا",
        "answer": "and fun",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "walaʿiban",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعِبًا",
        "answer": "and fun",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "walaʿiban",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَنَّاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We cursed them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "laʿannāhum",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَنَهُ",
        "answer": "has (been) cursed",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "laʿanahu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلُعِنُوا",
        "answer": "and they have been cursed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "waluʿinū",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لُعِنَ",
        "answer": "Were cursed",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "luʿina",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّغْوِ",
        "answer": "for the thoughtless utterances",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bil-laghwi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have cast",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-alqaynā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَامَسْتُمُ",
        "answer": "has (had) contact",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lāmastumu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوْمَةَ",
        "answer": "the blame",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "lawmata",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَائِمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a critic",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "lāimin",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسْتُمْ",
        "answer": "You are not",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "lastum",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "(as) provision",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "matāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "like",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِثْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and the like of it",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wamith'lahu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُ",
        "answer": "(is) similar",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "mith'lu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَضٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a disease",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "maraḍun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "ill",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "marḍā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَامْسَحُوا",
        "answer": "and wipe",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-im'saḥū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَامْسَحُوا",
        "answer": "then wipe",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-im'saḥū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَمَسَّنَّ",
        "answer": "surely will afflict",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "layamassanna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْسَكْنَ",
        "answer": "they catch",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "amsakna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "has power",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yamliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "(have) power",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "amliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْلِكَ",
        "answer": "will you have power",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tamlika",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "has power",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yamliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "the dominion",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلُوكًا",
        "answer": "kings",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "mulūkan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَهْدِ",
        "answer": "the cradle",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mahdi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتُ",
        "answer": "[the] death",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-mawtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] death",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيْتَةُ",
        "answer": "the dead animals",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-maytatu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَائِدَةً",
        "answer": "a table spread",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "māidatan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَائِدَةً",
        "answer": "a table spread",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "māidatan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَبِّئُهُمُ",
        "answer": "will inform them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yunabbi-uhumu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I inform you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "unabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَأَ",
        "answer": "the story",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "naba-a",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "Prophets",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "anbiyāa",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّبِيِّ",
        "answer": "and the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wal-nabiyi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّادِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the regretful",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-nādimīna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادِمِينَ",
        "answer": "regretful",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nādimīna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you make a call",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nādaytum",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٍ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "nadhīrin",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "and a warner",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wanadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزَّلُ",
        "answer": "is being revealed",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yunazzalu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلَ",
        "answer": "send down",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yunazzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We revealed",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) revealed",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has (been) revealed",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزِلْ",
        "answer": "send down",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "anzil",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنَزِّلُهَا",
        "answer": "(will) send it down",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "munazziluhā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءَ",
        "answer": "(with) the women",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-nisāa",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَسُوا",
        "answer": "and forgot",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wanasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَسُوا",
        "answer": "but they forgot",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fanasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّصُبِ",
        "answer": "the stone altars",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-nuṣubi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَنْصَابُ",
        "answer": "and (sacrifices at) altars",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wal-anṣābu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) Christians",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the Christians",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wal-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the Christians",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "wal-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the Christians",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "wal-naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصَارَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) Christians",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "naṣārā",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْصَارٍ",
        "answer": "helpers",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "anṣārin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّطِيحَةُ",
        "answer": "and that which is gored by horns",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-naṭīḥatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمَ",
        "answer": "(had) favored",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "anʿama",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "(of) the grazing livestock",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعَمِ",
        "answer": "the cattle",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-naʿami",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِي",
        "answer": "My Favor",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matī",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His Favor",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matahu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) Favor",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "niʿ'mata",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتَ",
        "answer": "(the) Favor",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "niʿ'mata",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) Favor",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "niʿ'mata",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتِي",
        "answer": "My Favor",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matī",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) Bliss",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-naʿīmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنْفُخُ",
        "answer": "then you breath",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fatanfukhu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِي",
        "answer": "(over) myself",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "nafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسُهُ",
        "answer": "his soul",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "nafsuhu",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "(for) a soul",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسَ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-nafsa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّفْسِ",
        "answer": "for the life",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "bil-nafsi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their souls",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their souls",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is to guard) yourselves",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِي",
        "answer": "myself",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "nafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِكَ",
        "answer": "Yourself",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "nafsika",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُ",
        "answer": "will profit",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعًا",
        "answer": "any benefit",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "nafʿan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُ",
        "answer": "He spends",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yunfiqu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفَوْا",
        "answer": "they be exiled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yunfaw",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقِيبًا",
        "answer": "leaders",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "naqīban",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْضِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their breaking",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "naqḍihim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْقِمُونَ",
        "answer": "you resent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tanqimūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَنْتَقِمُ",
        "answer": "then will take retribution",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fayantaqimu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتِقَامٍ",
        "answer": "(of) Retribution",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "intiqāmin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْكَرٍ",
        "answer": "wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "munkarin",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَالًا",
        "answer": "(as) an exemplary (punishment)",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nakālan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِنْهَاجًا",
        "answer": "and a clear way",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wamin'hājan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْهَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "forbid them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yanhāhumu",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَنَاهَوْنَ",
        "answer": "forbidding each other",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yatanāhawna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْتَهُوا",
        "answer": "they desist",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yantahū",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْتَهُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) the ones who abstain",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "muntahūna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "(the) fire",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "(will be) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورٌ",
        "answer": "a light",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "nūrun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّورِ",
        "answer": "the light",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-nūri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُورٌ",
        "answer": "and light",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "wanūrun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُورٌ",
        "answer": "and light",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "wanūrun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for mankind",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "(to) the people",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to the people",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنَالُهُ",
        "answer": "can reach it",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tanāluhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "Guides",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "and guides them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wayahdīhim",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "they (were) guided",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "yahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have been guided",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ih'tadaytum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهَدْيَ",
        "answer": "the sacrificial animals",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-hadya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدْيًا",
        "answer": "(as) an offering",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "hadyan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْهَدْيَ",
        "answer": "and the (animals) for offering",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "wal-hadya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "(was) Guidance",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "(was) Guidance",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and a Guidance",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) ridicule",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) ridicule",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "destroy",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُهِلَّ",
        "answer": "has been dedicated",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "uhilla",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَمَّ",
        "answer": "determined",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "hamma",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُهَيْمِنًا",
        "answer": "and a guardian",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wamuhayminan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادُوا",
        "answer": "(are) Jews",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "hādū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادُوا",
        "answer": "were Jews",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "hādū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادُوا",
        "answer": "became Jews",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "hādū",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "desired",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tahwā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their vain desires",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their vain desires",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَ",
        "answer": "(vain) desires",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ahwāa",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَهَيْئَةِ",
        "answer": "like the shape",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kahayati",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَالَ",
        "answer": "(the) consequence",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wabāla",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاثَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He bound you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wāthaqakum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِيثَاقَهُ",
        "answer": "and His covenant",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wamīthāqahu",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَ",
        "answer": "a Covenant",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "mīthāqa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their covenant",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "mīthāqahum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their covenant",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "mīthāqahum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَ",
        "answer": "a Covenant",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "mīthāqa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "you find",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَجِدَنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely you will find",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "latajidanna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَتَجِدَنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely you will find",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "walatajidanna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدْ",
        "answer": "find",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yajid",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "we found",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوُجُوهِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "biwujūhikum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهِهَا",
        "answer": "its (true) form",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wajhihā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "(the) One",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْتُ",
        "answer": "I inspired",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "awḥaytu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَدَّةً",
        "answer": "(in) affection",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "mawaddatan",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوَارِي",
        "answer": "to hide",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuwārī",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُوَارِيَ",
        "answer": "and hide",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-uwāriya",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْسَطِ",
        "answer": "average",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "awsaṭi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Encompassing",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَسِيلَةَ",
        "answer": "the means",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-wasīlata",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصِيلَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Wasilah",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waṣīlatin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَصِيَّةِ",
        "answer": "[the] a will",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-waṣiyati",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَاضِعِهِ",
        "answer": "their places",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mawāḍiʿihi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَاضِعِهِ",
        "answer": "their context",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "mawāḍiʿihi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "Has promised",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَوْعِظَةً",
        "answer": "and an admonition",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wamawʿiẓatan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "Fulfil",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَفَّيْتَنِي",
        "answer": "You raised me",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tawaffaytanī",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْقَدُوا",
        "answer": "they kindled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "awqadū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَوْقُوذَةُ",
        "answer": "and that which is hit fatally",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-mawqūdhatu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوقِعَ",
        "answer": "cause",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yūqiʿa",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "and feared (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "they fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "they fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "they fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And be conscious",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "So fear",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "fa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "And fear",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالتَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and [the] piety",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "wal-taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلتَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "to [the] piety",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "lilttaqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the God fearing",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the God conscious",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَتَوَكَّلِ",
        "answer": "so let put the trust",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "falyatawakkali",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَكَّلُوا",
        "answer": "then put your trust",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fatawakkalū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالِدَتِكَ",
        "answer": "your mother",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "wālidatika",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّوْنَ",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yatawallawna",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "takes them as allies",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yatawallahum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّ",
        "answer": "takes as an ally",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yatawalla",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّوْنَ",
        "answer": "taking as allies",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yatawallawna",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "tawallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوْلَيَانِ",
        "answer": "the former two ",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "l-awlayāni",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) allies",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) allies",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "awliyāu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُّكُمُ",
        "answer": "your ally",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "waliyyukumu",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) allies",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) allies",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَئِسَ",
        "answer": "(have) despaired",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ya-isa",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيْدِيَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your hands",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-aydiyakum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your hands",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aydiyahum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "aydiyahum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَكَ",
        "answer": "your hand",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yadaka",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدِيَ",
        "answer": "my hand",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yadiya",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَهُمَا",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "aydiyahumā",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "his hands",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "his hands",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "his hands",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدُ",
        "answer": "The Hand",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yadu",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَاهُ",
        "answer": "His Hands",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yadāhu",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hands",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَيْسِرُ",
        "answer": "and [the] games of chance",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wal-maysiru",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَيْسِرِ",
        "answer": "and gambling",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wal-maysiri",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوقِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) firmly believe",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yūqinūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَيَمَّمُوا",
        "answer": "then do tayyammum",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatayammamū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their oaths",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aymānihim",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your oaths",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aymānikum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَيْمَانَ",
        "answer": "(of) the oath",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-aymāna",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your oaths",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aymānikum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your oaths",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "aymānakum",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانٌ",
        "answer": "their oaths",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "aymānun",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their (others) oaths",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aymānihim",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of the) Day",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "and the Day",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wal-yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُ",
        "answer": "Day",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yawmu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "This day",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "This day",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "This day",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "al-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) day",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "5",
        "ayah": "109"
    }
]; 
export default words;